{
  "test" : "testing",
  "questions" : [
    {
      "name": "question-1",
      "question": "ln(e)+1=?",
      "choices": [
        {
          "name": "Window",
          "value": 1
        },
        {
          "name": "|+|",
          "value": 2
        },
        {
          "name": "2",
          "value": 3
        },
        {
          "name": "2.718",
          "value": 4
        }
      ],
      "correct_ans": 3
    },
    {
      "name": "question-2",
      "question": "What do horses eat?",
      "choices": [
        {
          "name": "Grass",
          "value": 1
        },
        {
          "name": "Meat",
          "value": 2
        },
        {
          "name": "Fish",
          "value": 3
        },
        {
          "name": "Bone",
          "value": 4
        }
      ],
      "correct_ans": 1
    },
    {
      "name": "question-3",
      "question": "What is Hg?",
      "choices": [
        {
          "name": "Hypergoal",
          "value": 1
        },
        {
          "name": "Mercury",
          "value": 2
        },
        {
          "name": "Venus",
          "value": 3
        },
        {
          "name": "None are correct",
          "value": 4
        }
      ],
      "correct_ans": 2
    },
    {
      "name": "question-4",
      "question": "Where does rice come from?",
      "choices": [
        {
          "name": "Cooking",
          "value": 1
        },
        {
          "name": "Farming",
          "value": 2
        },
        {
          "name": "Magic",
          "value": 3
        },
        {
          "name": "Outerspace",
          "value": 4
        }
      ],
      "correct_ans": 2
    },
    {
      "name": "question-5",
      "question": "What language that is latin?",
      "choices": [
        {
          "name": "Thai",
          "value": 1
        },
        {
          "name": "Japanese",
          "value": 2
        },
        {
          "name": "Korean",
          "value": 3
        },
        {
          "name": "French",
          "value": 4
        }
      ],
      "correct_ans": 4
    },
    {
      "name": "question-6",
      "question": "What meme is the craziest?",
      "choices": [
        {
          "name": "Trollface",
          "value": 1
        },
        {
          "name": "Rageface",
          "value": 2
        },
        {
          "name": "Forever alone",
          "value": 3
        },
        {
          "name": "Yao ming",
          "value": 4
        }
      ],
      "correct_ans": 1
    },
    {
      "name": "question-7",
      "question": "Which animal is the fastest of the given choices?",
      "choices": [
        {
          "name": "Snail",
          "value": 1
        },
        {
          "name": "Tortoise",
          "value": 2
        },
        {
          "name": "Rabbit",
          "value": 3
        },
        {
          "name": "Falcon",
          "value": 4
        }
      ],
      "correct_ans": 4
    },
    {
      "name": "question-8",
      "question": "What is the craziest game ever?",
      "choices": [
        {
          "name": "Jubeat",
          "value": 1
        },
        {
          "name": "Ikkagura",
          "value": 2
        },
        {
          "name": "Pokemon Go",
          "value": 3
        },
        {
          "name": "VRChat",
          "value": 4
        }
      ],
      "correct_ans": 3
    },
    {
      "name": "question-9",
      "question": "9+9*9-9/9=?",
      "choices": [
        {
          "name": "999999",
          "value": 1
        },
        {
          "name": "9",
          "value": 2
        },
        {
          "name": "89",
          "value": 3
        },
        {
          "name": "90",
          "value": 4
        }
      ],
      "correct_ans": 3
    },
    {
      "name": "question-10",
      "question": "How to call an adult female horse?",
      "choices": [
        {
          "name": "Mare",
          "value": 1
        },
        {
          "name": "Stallion",
          "value": 2
        },
        {
          "name": "Filly",
          "value": 3
        },
        {
          "name": "Colt",
          "value": 4
        }
      ],
      "correct_ans": 1
    },
    {
      "name": "question-11",
      "question": "H2O = ?",
      "choices": [
        {
          "name": "Fire",
          "value": 1
        },
        {
          "name": "Water",
          "value": 2
        },
        {
          "name": "Earth",
          "value": 3
        },
        {
          "name": "Wind",
          "value": 4
        }
      ],
      "correct_ans": 2
    },
    {
      "name": "question-12",
      "question": "Dog in japanese = ?",
      "choices": [
        {
          "name": "Inu",
          "value": 1
        },
        {
          "name": "Neko",
          "value": 2
        },
        {
          "name": "Nezumi",
          "value": 3
        },
        {
          "name": "Tori",
          "value": 4
        }
      ],
      "correct_ans": 1
    },
    {
      "name": "question-13",
      "question": "What emotion is harmful for keeping it too long the most?",
      "choices": [
        {
          "name": "Disgusted",
          "value": 1
        },
        {
          "name": "Scared",
          "value": 2
        },
        {
          "name": "Sad",
          "value": 3
        },
        {
          "name": "Rage",
          "value": 4
        }
      ],
      "correct_ans": 4
    },
    {
      "name": "question-14",
      "question": "Why do we go to school?",
      "choices": [
        {
          "name": "Because for money. Striaght forward as it is.",
          "value": 1
        },
        {
          "name": "Because for justice. To be good.",
          "value": 2
        },
        {
          "name": "Because parents and laws said it. Or else punishment.",
          "value": 3
        },
        {
          "name": "Because the real life jobs requires skills and knowledges to be efficient, help the society lives longer.",
          "value": 4
        }
      ],
      "correct_ans": 4
    },
    {
      "name": "question-15",
      "question": "Why engineering is important?",
      "choices": [
        {
          "name": "For just money.",
          "value": 1
        },
        {
          "name": "For creating more efficient works and make automations.",
          "value": 2
        },
        {
          "name": "For serving the social.",
          "value": 3
        },
        {
          "name": "For nothing",
          "value": 4
        }
      ],
      "correct_ans": 2
    }
  ]
}
